tsikot.com 2018-09-04

# Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time.

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and (under certain conditions) disclose your personal information and your options regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. By visiting the Website directly or through another site, you accept the practices described in this Policy.

Data protection is a matter of trust and your privacy is important to us. We shall therefore only use your name and other information which relates to you in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy.

You can visit the Website and browse without having to provide personal details. We will only collect information where it is necessary for us to do so and we will only collect information if it is relevant to our dealings with you. We will only keep your information for as long as we are either required to by law or as is relevant for the purposes for which it was collected. During your visit to the Website you remain anonymous and at no time can we identify you unless you voluntarily register and enter your details.

Tsikot.com website uses Google Analytics to help analyse how users use the site. The tool uses ‘cookies’, which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behaviour information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity for Tsikot.com.

## Data Collected

We may collect various pieces of information if you register, place an order, submit an enquiry, request a quote or apply for the service offer on the Website.

We collect, store and process your data when you register to the website, contact a seller, request a vehicle quote, submit and insurance and loan application. We may collect personal information including, but not limited to, your name, gender, date of birth, email address, postal and delivery address, telephone number, cellphone number and other required information to allow us to provide our services.

We will use the information you provide to enable us to process your orders and to provide you with the services and information offered through our website and which you request.

Further, we will use the information you provide to administer your account with us; verify and carry out financial transactions in relation to payments you make online; audit the downloading of data from our website; improve the layout and/or content of the pages of our website and customize them for users; identify visitors on our website; carry out research on our users' demographics; send you information we think you may find useful or which you have requested from us, including information about our products and services, provided you have indicated that you have not objected to being contacted for these purposes.

Subject to obtaining your consent we may contact you by email with details of other products and services. If you prefer not to receive any marketing communications from us, you can opt out at any time.

We may pass your details to third parties and partners in order to allow us to deliver the service requested, such as loan and insurance application.

If you choose to provide us with personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers.

## Other uses of your personal information

We may use your personal information for opinion and market research. Your details are anonymous and will only be used for statistical purposes. You can choose to opt out of this at any time or request the full deletion of your account details by [contacting us here](https://www.tsikot.com/contact-us).

We may also send you other information about us, the Website, our other websites, our products, sales promotions, our newsletters, anything relating to other companies in our group or our business partners. If you would prefer not to receive any of this additional information as detailed in this paragraph (or any part of it) please click the 'unsubscribe' link in any email that we send to you. Within 7 working days (days which are neither (i) a Saturday nor Sunday, nor (ii) a public holiday) of receipt of your instruction we will cease to send you information as requested. If your instruction is unclear we will contact you for clarification.

We may further anonymize data about users of the Website generally and use it for various purposes, including ascertaining the general location of the users and usage of certain aspects of the Website or a link contained in an email to those registered to receive them, and supplying that anonymized data to third parties such as publishers. However, that anonymized data will not be capable of identifying you personally.

## Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone’s rights, property or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. We may also share your personal information:

1\. Third parties to provide joint content and services (like registration, transactions and customer support), to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and violations of our policies, and to guide decisions about their products, services and communications. These third parties will use this information to send you marketing communications only if you’ve requested their services.

2\. Service providers under contract who help with our business operations (such as fraud investigations, bill collection, affiliate and rewards programs and customer support).

3\. Other third parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information (or about whom you are otherwise explicitly notified and consent to when using a specific service).

4\. Law enforcement agencies, other governmental agencies or third parties in response to a request for information relating to a criminal investigation, alleged illegal activity or any other activity that may expose us, you or any other Tsikot.com user to legal liability. The personal information we disclose may include your User ID and User ID history, name, city, county, telephone number, email address, fraud complaints and bidding and listing history or anything else that we deem relevant.

5\. Other agencies in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity, as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate, either under confidentiality agreement or as required by law. In such circumstances, we may disclose name, street address, city, county, postcode, country, phone number, email address and company name.

6\. Other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity. (Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. If your personal information will be used contrary to this policy, you will receive prior notice.)

## Third Parties

We may pass your details to other companies in our group. We may also pass your details to our agents, partners and subcontractors to help us with any of our uses of your data set out in this Privacy Policy. We may exchange information with third parties for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. We may transfer our databases containing your personal information if we sell our business or part of it. Other than as set out in this Privacy Policy, we shall NOT sell or disclose your personal data to third parties without obtaining your prior consent unless this is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy or unless we are required to do so by law. The Website may contain advertising of third parties and links to other sites or frames of other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those third parties or other sites, nor for any third party to whom we transfer your data in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

## No Spam, Spyware or Spoofing

We and our users do not tolerate spam. To report ‘Tsikot.com’ related spam or spoof emails, please report it to us. You may not use our communication tools to send spam or otherwise send content that would breach our User Agreement.

## Account Protection

Your email address, phone number and password are the key to your account. For passwords use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your ‘Tsikot.com’ password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify ‘Tsikot.com’ and change your password.

## Security

Your information is stored on our servers. We treat data as an asset that must be protected and use tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorised access and disclosure. However, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the site. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

We use encryption by using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) coding. While we are unable to guarantee 100% security, this makes it hard for a hacker to decrypt your details. You are strongly recommended not to send full credit or debit card details in unencrypted electronic communications with us.

If you are concerned about your data you have the right to request access to the personal data which we may hold or process about you. You have the right to require us to correct any inaccuracies in your data free of charge. At any stage you also have the right to ask us to stop using your personal data for direct marketing purposes.
